Kraushaar Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Addition to the Kraushaar Galleries Records, 1885-2006, Series 6:; (boxes 55-99, BV100; 38.4 linear feet)
  - Scrapbooks, 1901-1929, 6.8:
    - Scrapbook, 1901-1927, (Closed to researchers) (Box BV100, Folder 1)
May, 1932 Sculpture by Behn, Bourdelle, Geissbuhler, Lachaise, Maillol, Miller, Nadelman, Renoir, Young, Zorach; Decorative Panels by Max Kuehne, and Charles Prendergast
June-Aug., 1932 Paintings and Watercolors by American Artists
Oct.-Nov., 1932 Paintings, Watercolors, and Drawings by Various Artists
Jan., 1933 Paintings by Paul Bartlett
Jan.-Feb., 1933 Lithographs by Henri Fantin-Latour
Feb., 1933 Etchings of Dogs by Bert Cobb
Feb.-Mar., 1933 Paintings by American Artists
Feb.-Apr., 1933 Paintings by Contemporary Americans
Apr., 1933 Paintings by Maurice Prendergast
Oct., 1933 Exhibition of French Paintings, Watercolors, and Drawings
Oct.-Nov., 1933 Drawings by Emily W. Miles
Oct.-Nov., 1933 Exhibition of Etchings and Lithographs
Nov., 1933 Paintings and Watercolors by Henry E. Schnakenberg
Dec., 1933 Watercolors by Gifford Beal
Jan., 1934 Exhibition of Drawings by Denys Wortman for "Metropolitan Movies"
Summer, 1934 Paintings by Gifford Beal, Reynolds Beal, Isabel Bishop, Ann Brockman, Preston Dickinson, Guy Pène Du Bois, William J. Glackens, Richard Lahey, Ernest Lawson, George Luks, Harriette Miller, Maurice Prendergast, Henry E. Schnakenberg, and John Sloan
Oct.-Nov., 1934 Exhibition of Etchings and Lithographs
Nov.-Dec., 1934 Paintings by Gifford Beal
Mar., 1935 Complete Collection of Etchings by Mahonri Young
July-Aug., 1935 Paintings by American Artists including Gifford Beal, Reynolds Beal, Ann Brockman, Guy Pène Du Bois, William J. Glackens, Max Kuehne, Richard Lahey, Ernest Lawson, George Luks, Harriette G. Miller, Maurice Prendergast, Henry E. Schnakenberg, John Sloan, and Abraham Walkowitz
Oct.-Nov., 1935 Decorative Panels by Charles Prendergast
Nov., 1935 Exhibition of Paintings by H. E. Schnakenberg
Mar., 1936 Paintings by Louis Bouché
Apr., 1936 Paintings by Gifford Beal
Oct.-Nov., 1936 Loan Collection of French Paintings
Dec., 1936 Monotypes in Color by Maurice Prendergast
Jan., 1937 Recent Watercolors by H. E. Schnakenberg
Jan., 1937 Paintings of Flowers by William J. Glackens
Feb., 1937 Etchings by John Sloan
Feb., 1937 A Group of American Paintings
Sept., 1937 A Group of Paintings by Gifford Beal, Louis Bouché, Guy Pène Du Bois, William J. Glackens, Ernest Lawson, George Luks, Maurice Prendergast, Theodore Robinson, John Sloan, J. Alden Weir
Oct.-Nov., 1937 Decorative Panels by Charles Prendergast
Dec., 1937 American Watercolors
Jan.-Feb., 1938 Paintings by Gifford Beal
Feb.-Mar., 1938 Drawings by William Glackens, Guy Pène Du Bois, John Sloan, Denys Wortman
Apr., 1938 Paintings by Louis Bouché
May, 1938 Paintings and Pastels by Randall Davey
Oct., 1938 Selected Paintings by Modern French and American Artists
Nov., 1938 Paintings by Guy Pène Du Bois from 1908 to 1938
Nov., 1938 Paintings and Sculpture by Harriette G. Miller
Dec., 1938 Watercolors by Prendergast, Keller, Demuth, Wilcox and Others
Jan., 1939 Paintings by H. H. Newton
Oct., 1939 French and American Paintings
Oct.-Nov., 1939 Drawings by William Glackens of Spanish-American War Scenes
Nov., 1939 Paintings and Watercolors by Russell Cowles
Jan.-Feb., 1940 Recent Paintings by Louis Bouché
Feb.-Mar., 1940 Paintings by Henry Schnakenberg
Mar.-Apr., 1940 Paintings by Maurice Prendergast
Apr.-May, 1940 Watercolors by Charles Kaeselau
May-June, 1940 A Group of Recent Paintings by Gifford Beal, Russell Cowles, John Koch, Henry Schnakenberg, Esther Williams, Louis Bouché, Guy Pène Du Bois, Harriette G. Miller, John Sloan, Edmund Yaghjian
Oct., 1940 Drawings by American Artists
Nov., 1940 Walt Dehner
Mar., 1941 John Koch
May-June, 1941 Watercolors and Small Paintings by Gifford Beal
Oct.-Nov., 1941 Recent Paintings by Russell Cowles
Nov.-Dec., 1941 Paintings and Watercolors by Henry E. Schnakenberg
Dec., 1941 Charles Prendergast
Jan., 1942 Paintings by Samuel Brecher
Jan.-Feb., 1942 Recent Paintings by Guy Pène Du Bois
Mar.-Apr., 1942 Recent Paintings by Louis Bouché
Mar.-Apr., 1942 Illustrations by Boardman Robinson Commissioned by the Limited Editions Club for Edgar Lee Masters' "Spoon River Anthology"
Dec., 1942 Paintings from the Period of the Last War
Feb., 1943 Paintings and Watercolors by William Dean Fausett
Mar., 1943 Paintings by John Hartell
May-July, 1943 Watercolors by Contemporary American Artists
Feb.-Mar., 1944 Samuel Brecher
Feb.-Mar., 1944 Paintings, Gouaches, and Drawings by Andrée Ruellan
Mar., 1944 Vaughn Flannery
Mar.-Apr., 1944 Recent Paintings by Russell Cowles
Apr.-May, 1944 Recent Paintings by Louis Bouché
May-June, 1944 Retrospective Exhibition of Paintings and Watercolors by Henry G. Keller
Oct., 1944 Esther Williams
Nov.-Dec., 1944 Paintings and Watercolors of France by Maurice Prendergast
Dec., 1944 William J. Glackens Sixth Memorial Exhibition
Dec., 1944 Kraushaar Galleries Sixtieth Anniversary Exhibition of Paintings by William J. Glackens, Ernest Lawson, George Luks, Maurice Prendergast, and John Sloan
Jan.-Feb., 1945 Paintings by Gifford Beal
Feb.-Mar., 1945 Paintings by Andrée Ruellan
Apr.-May, 1945 Charles Locke
May-June, 1945 William Dean Fausett
Oct., 1945 Paintings by John Hartell
Nov.-Dec., 1945 Recent Watercolors by Marion Monks Chase
Nov.-Dec., 1945 Gouaches by Cecil Bell
Dec., 1945 Memorial Exhibition of Paintings and Watercolors by Ann Brockman
undated, 1946 Russell Cowles
Jan.-Feb., 1946 Richard Lahey
Feb., 1946 John Koch
Feb.-Mar., 1946 Paintings by Ernst Halberstadt
Mar., 1946 Paintings of Mexico and Guatemala by Henry E. Schnakenberg
Mar., 1946 Iver Rose
Apr., 1946 Louis Bouché
Apr.-May, 1946 Russell Cowles
May-June, 1946 Paintings by Bernard Arnest, Charles Harsanyi, Irving Katzenstein, Anna Licht, James Penney, Etienne Ret, and Vernon Smith
Sept., 1946 Retrospective Exhibition of the Work of Boardman Robinson
Nov., 1946 Guy Pène Du Bois
Nov.-Dec., 1946 William J. Glackens Eighth Memorial Exhibition
Jan., 1947 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1947 Sculpture by Robert Laurent
Feb.-Mar., 1947 Paintings by Iver Rose
Feb.-Mar., 1947 Recent Paintings by Vernon Smith
Apr., 1947 Charles Prendergast
Apr., 1947 Louis Bouché
Apr.-May, 1947 Esther Williams
Oct.-Nov., 1947 Anna Licht
Nov., 1947 William J. Glackens Ninth Memorial Exhibition, with Works by Lenna Glackens
Mar., 1948 Russell Cowles
Apr.-May, 1948 Bernard Arnest
Aug.-Sept., 1948 New York Paintings and Watercolors
Oct.-Nov., 1948 Kenneth Evett
Nov.-Dec., 1948 Watercolors and Pastels by Harriette G. Miller
Jan.-Feb., 1949 John Hartell
Sept.-Oct., 1949 Contemporary American Watercolors and Gouaches
Oct., 1949 Contemporary Paintings
Jan., 1950 Maurice Prendergast Retrospective of Oils and Watercolors
Jan.-Feb., 1950 James Penney
Feb.-Mar., 1950 Paintings by Karl Schrag
Mar.-Apr., 1950 Russell Cowles
Jan.-Feb., 1951 William Sommer
Feb., 1951 Prints and Drawings by Various Artists
Feb., 1951 Paintings by Louis Bouché
Mar., 1951 Kenneth Evett
Apr.-May, 1951 Paintings by Gallery Artists
May-July, 1951 Contemporary American Watercolors
July-Aug., 1951 Paintings on the Summer Theme
Sept.-Oct., 1951 Vaughn Flannery
Oct.-Nov., 1951 Recent Paintings by Gallery Artists
Nov., 1951 Paintings by John Koch
Nov.-Dec., 1951 Joe Lasker
Dec., 1951 Small Prints and Drawings
Jan., 1952 Recent Gouaches by William Kienbusch
Jan., 1952 John Sloan: Recent Etchings from 1944-1951, and Etchings and Drawings Selected from All Periods of His Career
Feb.-Mar., 1952 Andrée Ruellan
Mar.-Apr., 1952 Bernard Arnest
Apr.-May, 1952 Recent Sculpture by Robert Laurent
May, 1952 Recent Paintings by Contemporary American Artists
May-June, 1952 Watercolors by Joseph Barber, Edward Christiana, Walt Dehner, Sidney Eaton, Wray Manning, and Woldemar Neufeld
July-Aug., 1952 Color Prints (Woodcuts, Etchings, and Lithographs) by Eleanor Coen, Caroline Durieux, Max Kahn, Tom Lias, Woldemar Neufeld, James Penney, George Remaily, Ann Ryan, and Karl Schrag
Nov., 1952 Karl Schrag
Dec., 1952-Jan. 1953 Eight Oregon Artists
Jan., 1953 Charles Prendergast Memorial Exhibition
Jan.-Feb., 1953 John Hartell
May, 1953 John Heliker
June, 1953 Humbert Alberizio, Vaughn Flannery, William Kienbusch, George Rickey, Andrée Ruellan, and Karl Schrag
Sept., 1953 Works by Gifford Beal, Kenneth Evett, Tom Hardy, John Koch, and James Lechay
Sept.-Oct., 1953 Paintings by Glackens, Lawson, Prendergast, Sloan
Oct.-Nov., 1953 Paintings by E. Powis Jones
Oct.-Nov., 1953 Recent Works by John Koch
Nov., 1953 Kenneth Evett: Drawings from Greek Mythology
Nov.-Dec., 1953 Recent Metal Sculptures by Tom Hardy
Nov.-Dec., 1953 Pastels, Drawings and Prints by Peggy Bacon
Nov.-Dec., 1953 Recent Paintings by Ralph Dubin
Feb.-Mar., 1954 Russell Cowles
Mar.-Apr., 1954 James Penney
Nov.-Dec., 1954 Tom Hardy: Metal Sculptures
Jan., 1955 Mobiles, Machines, and Kinetic Sculpture by George Rickey
Jan.-Feb., 1955 James Lechay
Feb., 1955 Mobiles by George Rickey
Feb.-Mar., 1955 Drawings, Etchings, and Lithographs by John Sloan (with a selection of prints by artists whose work influenced him in his early years: Rembrandt, Hogarth, Goya, Rops, Daumier, Rowlandson and others, to mark the publication of John Sloan: A Painter's Life by Van Wyck Brooks)
Mar.-Apr., 1955 Jane Wasey
Apr., 1955 Recent Work by Joe Lasker
May-June, 1955 Sculpture and Drawings by Contemporary American Artists
Jan., 1956 Carl Morris
Jan.-Feb., 1956 John Laurent
Feb.-Mar., 1956 William Kienbusch
Mar., 1956 Andrée Ruellan
Mar.-Apr., 1956 Karl Schrag
Apr.-May, 1956 John Heliker
May, 1956 Monotypes by Maurice Prendergast
Oct., 1956 The Eight
Jan.-Feb., 1957 Paintings by John Hartell
Apr., 1957 James Penney
Apr.-May, 1957 John Heliker
May-June, 1957 Fourteen Painter-Printmakers (American Federation of Arts exhibition)
June-July, 1957 20th Century American Artists
Nov., 1957 William Glackens and His Friends (based on the book by Ira Glackens)
Nov., 1957 Marguerite Zorach
Jan., 1958 Gouches, Drawings and Small Glyphs by Ulfert Wilke
Jan.-Feb., 1958 Tom Hardy
Feb.-Mar., 1958 John Koch
Feb.-Mar., 1958 Still Life Exhibition with Works by William J. Glackens and Maurice Prendergast
Feb.-Mar., 1958 Cecil Bell
Mar., 1958 Karl Schrag
Mar., 1958 Carl Morris
Mar.-Apr., 1958 Louis Bouché
Apr., 1958 Paintings and Drawings by Joe Lasker
Apr.-May, 1958 Paintings and Drawings by Walter Feldman
Apr.-May, 1958 Sculpture by Henry Mitchell
May-June, 1958 Works in Casein and Gouache by Bernard Arnest, William Kienbusch, Carl Morris, and Karl Schrag
July, 1958 Still Life Paintings and Watercolors by American Artists
Oct.-Nov., 1958 Kenneth Evett
Nov., 1958 Elsie Manville
Nov.-Dec., 1958 John Laurent
Jan., 1959 Kinetic Sculpture by George Rickey
Jan.-Feb., 1959 Bernard Arnest
Mar., 1959 Karl Schrag
Mar.-Apr., 1959 Paintings by Joe Lasker
Apr.-May, 1959 Henry Mitchell
Sept.-Oct., 1959 Robert Searle
Oct.-Nov., 1959 Russell Cowles
Nov., 1959 Caseins and Paintings by William Kienbusch
Dec., 1959 Paintings by Vaughn Flannery
Feb., 1960 James Lechay
Apr., 1960 Landscapes by John Sloan
Apr.-May, 1960 John Guerin
May-June, 1960 Drawings and Small Sculpture by Gallery Artists
Oct., 1960 Ainslie Burke
Oct.-Nov., 1960 Leon Goldin
Nov.-Dec., 1960 Ulfert Wilke
Jan., 1961 Leonard DeLonga
Jan., 1961 Kenneth Evett
Jan.-Feb., 1961 Walter Feldman
Feb.-Mar., 1961 Watercolors and Pastels by Early Twentieth-Century American Artists
Mar., 1961 Paintings by Ralph Dubin
Mar.-Apr., 1961 James Penney
Apr.-May, 1961 John Koch
June, 1961 Works by Humbert Albrizio, Bernard Arnest, Cecil Bell, Louis Bouché, Ralph Dubin, Kenneth Evett, Walter Feldman, John Hartell, John Heliker, William Kienbusch, John Koch, Robert Laurent, James Lechay, Elsie Manville, Henry Mitchell, James Penney, George Rickey, Andrée Ruellan, Henry E. Schnakenberg, Karl Schrag, Jane Wasey, and Marguerite Zorach
Sept., 1961 Works by Contemporary Americans
Oct., 1961 George Rickey: Kinetic Sculpture
Oct.-Nov., 1961 Carl Morris
Nov.-Dec., 1961 Peggy Bacon
Dec., 1961 Selected Works by Twentieth-Century Americans
Jan., 1962 Polymer Resin and Sumi Ink Paintings by Kenneth Evett
Jan.-Feb., 1962 Louis Bouché
Feb.-Mar., 1962 Karl Schrag
Mar., 1962 Marguerite Zorach
Apr., 1962 John Laurent
Apr.-May, 1962 Sculpture by Tom Hardy
May-June, 1962 Drawings by Contemporary American Artists
July-Aug., 1962 Group Exhibitions - Paintings, Drawings and Sculpture by 20th Century American Artists
Oct., 1962 Bernard Arnest
Feb., 1963 William Kienbusch
Feb.-Mar., 1963 John Guerin
Mar., 1963 John Hartell
Sept.-Oct., 1963 Andrée Ruellan
Oct.-Nov., 1963 Ainslie Burke
Nov., 1963 Walter Feldman
Dec., 1963 Drawings by John Koch
Dec., 1963 Paintings by Contemporary Americans
Jan., 1964 Leonard DeLonga
Jan.-Feb., 1964 Joe Lasker
Feb.-Mar., 1964 Leon Goldin
Mar., 1964 Paintings by Ralph Dubin
Apr., 1964 Carl Morris
Apr.-May, 1964 Paintings and Drawings by John Heliker
Oct.-Nov., 1964 Louis Bouché
Nov.-Dec., 1964 Karl Schrag
Dec., 1964 Kenneth Evett
Feb., 1965 Russell Cowles
Feb.-Mar., 1965 James Lechay
Mar.-Apr., 1965 James Penney
Apr.-May, 1965 Gifford Beal
Feb., 1966 Dennis Leon
Feb.-Mar., 1966 Henry Schnakenberg
Mar.-Apr., 1966 John Hartell
Apr., 1966 Elsie Manville
Oct., 1966 Contrasts - Early and Late Works by Selected Contemporaries
Oct.-Nov., 1966 Tom Hardy
Nov.-Dec., 1966 Francis Chapin
Dec., 1966-Jan., 1967 Karl Schrag: Etchings and Lithographs
Jan.-Feb., 1967 Leonard DeLonga
Feb.-Mar., 1967 Carl Morris
Mar.-Apr., 1967 Ainslie Burke
Apr.-May, 1967 John Heliker: Paintings, Drawings, and Watercolors
May-June, 1967 William Glackens
Oct., 1967 Kenneth Callahan
Oct.-Nov., 1967 John Laurent
Jan.-Feb., 1968 Dennis Leon
Feb.-Mar., 1968 Robert La Hotan
Apr., 1968 John Guerin
Apr.-May, 1968 Leon Goldin
Sept.-Oct., 1968 Contemporary Sculpture and Drawings
Oct.-Nov., 1968 Karl Schrag
Nov.-Dec., 1968 James Lechay: Portraits and Landscapes
Dec., 1968-Jan., 1969 Group Exhibition
Jan., 1969 Elsie Manville
Mar., 1969 Kenneth Evett
Apr.-May, 1969 James Penney
Sept.-Oct., 1969 New Works by Contemporary Artists
Oct.-Nov., 1969 John Hartell: Exhibition
Nov., 1969 Peggy Bacon
Dec., 1969 Selected Examples by American Artists 1900-1930
Jan., 1970 Leonard DeLonga
Feb., 1970 Joe Lasker
Mar., 1970 Group Exhibition
Mar.-Apr., 1970 Dennis Leon
Apr.-May, 1970 Jerome Myers
Oct.-Nov., 1970 Tom Hardy
Jan.-Feb., 1971 Jane Wasey
Mar.-Apr., 1971 Kenneth Callahan
Oct., 1971 Ainslie Burke
Nov.-Dec., 1971 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1972 John Koch
Mar.-Apr., 1972 Robert La Hotan
Apr.-May, 1972 Leon Goldin
May-June, 1972 Selected Works by 20th Century Americans
Sept.-Oct., 1972 Gallery Collection: American Watercolors and Drawings
Oct.-Nov., 1972 John Hartell
Nov.-Dec., 1972 Peggy Bacon
Dec., 1972 20th Century Americans
Jan., 1973 Leonard DeLonga
Feb., 1973 Carl Morris
Mar., 1973 James Lechay
Mar.-Apr., 1973 Russell Cowles: Landscape Paintings
Apr.-May, 1973 Jerome Witkin
May-June, 1973 Kenneth Evett: Watercolors
Oct.-Nov., 1973 Kenneth Callahan
Jan., 1974 Joe Lasker
Jan.-Feb., 1974 Bernard Arnest
Feb.-Mar., 1974 Concetta Scaravaglione
Oct., 1974 Ainslie Burke
Oct.-Nov., 1974 James Penney
Jan., 1975 Tom Hardy
Jan.-Feb., 1975 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1975 Robert La Hotan
Mar.-Apr., 1975 William Kienbusch
Apr., 1975 Elsie Manville
Apr.-May, 1975 Gifford Beal
Oct.-Nov., 1975 John Hartell
Nov., 1975 Daniel O'Sullivan
Mar., 1976 Jerome Witkin
May, 1976 Linda Sokolowski
Sept.-Oct., 1976 Joe Lasker, Illustrations from Merry Ever After
Oct., 1976 Leonard DeLonga
Nov.-Dec., 1976 Kenneth Callahan
Jan., 1977 James Lechay
Mar., 1977 Karl Schrag
Mar.-Apr., 1977 David Cantine
Oct.-Nov., 1977 John Hartell
Nov.-Dec., 1977 Ainslie Burke
Feb., 1978 Robert La Hotan
Apr., 1978 Elsie Manville
Oct., 1978 Tom Hardy
Oct.-Nov., 1978 Jerome Witkin
Jan.-Feb., 1979 Joe Lasker
Feb., 1979 Kenneth Evett
Feb.-Mar., 1979 Karl Schrag
Mar.-Apr., 1979 Carl Morris
Apr.-May, 1979 Linda Sokolowski
Oct.-Nov., 1979 Daniel O'Sullivan
Feb.-Mar., 1980 Kenneth Callahan
Mar., 1980 Ainslie Burke
Oct., 1980 John Hartell
Jan., 1981 Leonard DeLonga
Feb., 1981 James Lechay
Feb.-Mar., 1981 Robert La Hotan
Mar.-Apr., 1981 Jerry Atkins
Apr.-May, 1981 Ben Frank Moss
Jan.-Feb., 1982 Jerome Witkin
Feb.-Mar., 1982 Elsie Manville
Mar.-Apr., 1982 Karl Schrag
Apr.-May, 1982 Linda Sokolowski
May-June, 1982 David Cantine
Sept.-Oct., 1982 Kenneth Callahan
Oct.-Nov., 1982 Joe Lasker
Nov.-Dec., 1982 Daniel O'Sullivan
Jan.-Feb., 1983 William Kienbusch: Memorial Exhibition
Feb.-Mar., 1983 Jerry Atkins
Mar.-Apr., 1983 John Hartell
Apr.-May, 1983 John Heliker
May-June, 1983 Kenneth Evett
Oct., 1983 Concetta Scaravaglione
Oct.-Nov., 1983 Ben Frank Moss
Nov.-Dec., 1983 Russell Cowles
Dec., 1983-Jan., 1984 20th Century Americans
Jan.-Feb., 1984 Marguerite Zorach: Paintings at Home and Abroad
Feb.-Mar., 1984 Robert La Hotan
Mar., 1984 David Smalley
Apr., 1984 Carl Morris
May, 1984 Karl Schrag
July, 1984 Drawings by 20th Century Americans
July-Aug., 1984 Collages and Drawings by Joseph Heil
Aug.-Sept., 1984 Drawings and Prints by Tom Hardy
Sept.-Oct., 1984 James Penney: Memorial Exhibition
Oct.-Nov., 1984 Paintings and Drawings by Leon Goldin
Nov.-Dec., 1984 Isabelle Siegel
Dec., 1984-Jan., 1985 Group Exhibition: Contemporary American Paintings and Sculpture
Jan.-Feb., 1985 James Lechay
Feb.-Mar., 1985 Ainslie Burke
Mar., 1985 Karen Breunig
Apr., 1985 Kenneth Callahan
Oct., 1985 Elsie Manville
Oct.-Nov., 1985 William Glackens
Jan.-Feb., 1986 Linda Sokolowski
Feb.-Mar., 1986 Jerry Atkins
Apr.-May, 1986 Jane Wasey
Oct.-Nov., 1986 John Hartell
Nov.-Dec., 1986 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1987 Kenneth Evett
Apr.-May, 1987 Ben Frank Moss
May-June, 1987 David Smalley
Oct.-Nov., 1987 Isabelle Siegel
Feb.-Mar., 1988 Karen Breunig
Mar.-Apr., 1988 Leon Goldin
Sept.-Oct., 1988 Elsie Manville
Oct.-Nov., 1988 James Lechay
Jan.-Feb., 1989 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1989 Linda Sokolowski
Jan.-Feb., 1990 Kenneth Callahan: Works of the Fifties
Jan.-Feb., 1990 Gifford Beal: Watercolors
Mar., 1990 Robert La Hotan: Recent Paintings
Mar.-Apr., 1990 Sonia Gechtoff: New Paintings
May-June, 1990 David Smalley: Recent Sculpture
May-June, 1990 Andrée Ruellan: Sixty Years of Drawing...
Oct., 1990 Isabelle Siegel
Nov., 1990 Leon Goldin
Jan.-Feb., 1991 Karl Schrag
Feb.-Mar., 1991 Joe Lasker
Apr., 1991 Ainslie Burke
Nov.-Dec., 1991 Linda Sokolowski: Oils, Collages, Monotypes
Dec., 1991-Jan., 1992 Elsie Manville: Small Works on Paper
Mar., 1992 Tabitha Vevers
May-June, 1992 Sonia Gechtoff
Oct.-Nov., 1992 James Lechay
Nov.-Dec., 1992 Karl Schrag
Mar., 1993 Leon Goldin: Works on Paper
Apr.-May, 1993 Robert La Hotan
Oct., 1993 David Smalley: Sculpture Inside and Out
Oct., 1993 Andrée Ruellan: Works on Paper 1920-1980
Mar.-Apr., 1994 Kenneth Evett: Travels: Themes and Variations (Watercolors of Italy, Greece, Arizona, Maine and California)
Mar.-Apr., 1994 Tabitha Vevers
Oct.-Nov., 1994 Linda Sokolowski
Nov.-Dec., 1994 Karl Schrag
Jan.-Feb., 1995 Langdon Quin
Mar.-Apr., 1995 Robert La Hotan
Sept.-Oct., 1995 Sonia Gechtoff
Jan.-Feb., 1996 Elsie Manville: Paintings and Works on Paper
Oct.-Nov., 1996 Karl Schrag: A Self Portrait Retrospective, 1940-1995
Jan.-Feb., 1997 Joe Lasker: Paintings and Watercolors
Mar.-Apr., 1997 Tabitha Vevers
Oct.-Nov., 1997 James Lechay
Feb.-Mar., 1998 Linda Sokolowski: Canyon Suite: Works from the Southwest
Mar.-Apr., 1998 Leon Goldin: Paintings on Paper
Sept.-Oct., 1998 Sonia Gechtoff: Mysteries in the Sphere
Oct.-Nov., 1998 Langdon Quin: Recent Paintings
Nov.-Dec., 1998 John Gill
Jan.-Feb., 1999 Robert La Hotan
Feb.-Mar., 1999 Ann Sperry: Where Is Your Heart
Nov.-Dec., 1999 Kathryn Wall
Jan.-Feb., 2000 Elsie Manville
Sept.-Oct., 2000 Joe Lasker
Oct.-Nov., 2000 James Lechay
Oct.-Nov., 2000 Tabitha Vevers
May-June, 2001 Kenneth Callahan: Drawings
Dec., 2001-Jan., 2002 Sur La Table: A Selection of Paintings and Works on Paper
Jan.-Feb., 2002 Karl Schrag: Theme and Variations II: The Meadow
undated, 2003 Ann Sperry
Jan.-Feb., 2003 Andrée Ruellan: Works on Paper from the 1920s and 1930s
Oct.-Nov., 2003 Joe Lasker: Muses and Amusements
Nov.-Dec., 2003 Tabitha Vevers
Mar.-Apr., 2004 Leon Goldin: Five Decades of Works on Paper
May-July, 2004 Anne Frank: A Private Photo Album
Jan.-Feb., 2005 John Gill: Ceramics
Sept.-Oct., 2005 Karl Schrag: The Painter of Bright Nights